<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
        <title>KG7QIN</title>
        <description>KG7QIN - Stacy Olivas (KG7QIN)</description>
        <link>http://kg7qin.github.io</link>
        <atom:link href="http://kg7qin.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 12:53:32 -0700</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 12:53:32 -0700</pubDate>
        <ttl>60</ttl>


        <item>
                <title>Porting AllStarLink to Asterisk 1.8.32.3</title>
                <description>
&lt;h1 id=&quot;allstarlinkasterisk-18-port&quot;&gt;AllStarLink/Asterisk 1.8 Port&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Main site:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://allstarlink.org&quot;&gt;AllStarLink Network&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I initially did most of the work on this back in October/November 2015.  At the time, I had quite a bit of free time
on my hands, as I was retiring from the US Navy after 20 years of active duty service and looking for a new job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After my initial push to get most of the stuff converted, and there are still a few modules that need to be ported over, 
ended up stopping for abit with the eventual plan to pick this back up.  I finally decided to release this on Github so that:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The code doesn’t get lost in time.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I hope that I can start collaborating with others on this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d really like to see the AllStarLink network move forward, and think that Jim Dixon (et all) have done a really great job on 
getting it up and keeping it running.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With any project, if things stagnate (regardless of how great they work), then there is a possibility that it will eventually
die off.  I’d like to see AllStarLink eventually move from 1.4 to 1.8 and then onto a more recent and supported version of Asterisk
like 13.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Repository:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/KG7QIN/AllStarLink-Asterisk-1.8&quot;&gt;AllStarLink-Asterisk-1.8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>http://kg7qin.github.io/asterisk/2016/04/23/allstarlink-asterisk-1.8</link>
                <guid>http://kg7qin.github.io/asterisk/2016/04/23/allstarlink-asterisk-1.8</guid>
                <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Asterisk for AllStarLink Network</title>
                <description>
&lt;h1 id=&quot;allstarlinkasterisk&quot;&gt;AllStarLink/Asterisk&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Main site:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://allstarlink.org&quot;&gt;AllStarLink Network&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note:  Both of these repositories were made a while ago as a place to put the code for others to use.  They currently are
not maintained in any way, so you are on your own if you use them.  The ideal way to use these repositories would be to
fork them, so if you make any changes or find bugs, you can make the changes and send me a pull request later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Repository:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/KG7QIN/AllStarLink&quot;&gt;AllStarLink&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is my inital contribution to the AllStar Link Network/Asterisk.  There, you will find the files I pushed to the repo for getting the forked 
version of Asterisk to compile on a modern (3.x+) Linux Kernel.  It runs, and I’ve successfully run this one several of my 
machines for connecting to the AllStarLink Network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This also contains the ports of the pathches needed for DAHDI to 2.10.2+2.10.2-complete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Repository:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/KG7QIN/AllStarLink-FreeBSD&quot;&gt;AllStarLink-FreeBSD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, there exists an untested port of the patches to the DAHDI driver for FreeBSD.  This was modified from the 
FreeBSD ports tree.  It compiles, runs and loads into the FreeBSD Kernel without a panic (a good thing!)&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>http://kg7qin.github.io/asterisk/2015/10/20/asterisk-for-allstar-link-network</link>
                <guid>http://kg7qin.github.io/asterisk/2015/10/20/asterisk-for-allstar-link-network</guid>
                <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>


</channel>
</rss>
